https://meetings.cshl.edu/home.aspx?name=privacy

Data Privacy Policy
(updated May 25 2018)
Cold Spring Harbor Laboratory (CSHL) Meetings & Courses Program is committed to protecting personal data submitted to us by meetings and course participants in compliance with US and international laws.
The types of personal information that we collect depend on your intended activity at CSHL. Typically, at minimum, we collect name, primary address, phone and email, professional details such as career stage, labhead etc. For active participation in our meetings, we request submission of a one-page abstract used to guide selection of talks and posters and to arrange the schedule of the meeting. Abstract submission requires limited personal information of the abstract authors. For courses, applicants are asked to submit personal statements and/or resumes, financial aid requests and letters of reference. Given that 90% of participants arrange their accommodation through CSHL and all catering is handled on campus, we request gender information, special dietary requests etc. We also request demographic information on a voluntary basis for US federal reporting purposes.
CSHL Meetings & Courses Program is the sole repository of the information collected through our website. We do not sell, rent or share personal information with other organizations. Anonymized data is used in federal grant applications. Payment information provided during registration is processed through standard encryption protocols by a third party provider (Authorize.net) and is not stored at CSHL.
CSHL Meetings & Courses Program utilize personal information provided by you to organize the meeting or course that you are attending. None of this information is shared with third party organizations. We currently use past participation at a meeting or course to alert you of highly related activities and events offered by us in the future. Any subsequent correspondence from us includes the option to permanently opt out of future notifications.
If you think that our program is not abiding by its posted Data Privacy policy, please contact us via email: meetings@cshl.edu, or by mail at Cold Spring Harbor Laboratory Meetings & Courses Program, 1 Bungtown Road, Cold Spring Harbor NY 11724.
